PG 560, Connecticut Group Portraits Collection
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut group portraits collection
1864-2007
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut State Library (collector)
3.5 cubic feet
This collection contains over 100 group portraits of local and state officials, governors & their staff, Connecticut lawyers and members of local organizaitions.
PG560
Multiple
Scope and Content
This collection contains over 100 group portraits of local and state officials, governors & their staff, Connecticut lawyers and members of local organizaitions. Not included are Connecticut military groups who form another picture group (PG 570).
Arrangement
The portraits are arranged categorically.
Other Finding Aid
A portrait index available at the History and Genealogy reference desk lists individual names.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Governors -- Connecticut; Lawyers -- Connecticut; Judges -- Connecticut; New London County Bar Association
Document Types:
Photographs
Restrictions on Access
Some of these records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Governors & staff, 1864-1939, undated; T002672/T002672M
  - Gov. Buckingham & staff, 1864 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Hawley & staff, circa 1866-1867 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Cooke & Foot Guard, circa 1897-1899 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Chamberlain & Horse Guard, 1903 (Box Box 1)
  - Gov. Chamberlain & Foot Guard, 1903 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Woodruff, Lt. Gov. Lake & Attorney General Holcomb, 1909 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Weeks & President Taft in Norwich, circa 1909-1911 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Holcomb & Foot Guard, circa 1915-1921 (Box Map case)
  - Gov. Lake & state officials, 1921 (Box Box 1)
  - Gov. Bingham, Lt. Gov. Trumbull & Foot Guard, 1925 (Box Box 1)
  - Gov. Raymond Baldwin & state officials, 1939 (Box Box 1)
  - Three great war governors, undated (Box Box 1)
  - Governors still living in 1919 (Box Box 1)
- Lawyers, 1899-2007
  - T002672M
    - Bench and bar of Connecticut, 1917 (Box Map case)
    - Bench and bar, Hartford County, 1899 (Box Map case)
    - Bench and bar, Hartford County, 1940 (Box Map case)
    - Bench and bar, New London County, 1899 (Box Map case)
  - 2009-028
    - Bench & bar, New London County, 1899; 23 x 26 in.
    - New London lawyers and judges, circa 1910; 8 x 10 in.
    - New London lawyers and judges, circa 1910; 8 x 10 in.
    - Bench & bar, New London County, 1949; 26 x 37 in., framed
    - New London County Bar Association, 1970; 11 x 14 in.
    - New London County Bar Association, 1978; 16 x 20 in.
    - New London County Bar Association, 2007; 16 x 20 in., framed
- Local groups, circa 1870-1950, undated; T002672/T002672M
  - Canton Congregational Church Bicentennial Choir, 1950 (Box Box 1)
  - C. A. C. Class of 1899 (Box Map case)
    Possibly Connecticut Agricultural College.
  - Connecticut mayors, undated (Box Box 1)
  - C.V.I. Oasis Club, 1926 (Box Box 1)
  - D.A.R. Litchfield Chapter in costume, undated (Box Box 1)
  - New Haven wheel shop, circa 1870 (Box Box 1)
  - Nutmeg Fishing Club, circa 1920-1929 (Box Box 1)
  - Sons of Connecticut, Officers, undated (Box Box 1)
  - South Norwalk teachers, circa 1890-1899 (Box Box 1)
  - Stanley Memorial Church Group, New Britain, 1905 (Box Map case)
  - Sutler Bros. mill workers, undated (Box Map case)
  - Wesleyan University Class of 1892/93 reunion, undated (Box Box 1)
  - Yale University Class of 1900 reunion, 1925 (Box Map case)
  - Unidentified group near shore, circa 1860-1869 (Box Box 1)
- Local groups - Hartford, circa 1876-1929, undated; T002672/T002672M
  - Connecticut Institute for the Blind, undated (Box Box 1)
  - Hartford Dark Blues, 1876 (Box Box 1)
    The Hartford Dark Blues were a baseball team.
  - Hartford Board of Aldermen, 1918 (Box Box 1)
  - Hartford City Guard, 1897 (Box Box 1)
  - Hartford City officials, circa 1920-1929 (Box Box 1)
    Draft Board, Legal Advisory Board, Medical Advisory Board.
  - Hartford Court of Common Council, circa 1907-1908 (Box Map case)
  - Hartford Hospital Class of 1892 (Box Box 1)
  - Hartford Public High School Class of 1918 (Box Map case)
  - "Old Timers" dinner, 1923 (Box Map case)
  - Plimpton Manufacturing Co. "Old Timers", undated (Box Box 1)
  - Volunteer Firemen's Association, undated (Box Box 1)
- State officials, circa 1905-1940; T002672/T002672M
  - Appropriations Committee, circa 1940 (Box Box 1)
    This identification is not certain.
  - Israel Putnam Memorial Campground Commission, 1905 (Box Box 1)
  - State Board of Agriculture, 1912 (Box Map case)
  - State Police Association, 1912 (Box Box 1)
  - State officials still living in 1919 (Box Box 1)
  - Gov. Ella T. Grasso and State Library Board, 1976 (Box Box 1)
    Added March 1991.
- Supreme Court judges, circa 1868-1950; T002672M
  - circa 1868-1870 (Box Map case)
  - circa 1900-1909 (Box Map case)
  - 1908 (Box Map case)
  - 1917 (Box Map case)
  - circa 1920-1929 (Box Map case)
  - circa 1927-1930 (Box Map case)
  - 1939 (Box Map case)
  - 1947 (Box Map case)
  - 1950 (Box Map case)